Two legendary enemies unite to fight the charging white beast!!
The White Buffalo is a western, adventure, action
film directed by J. Lee Thompson.
In this strange western version of Moby Dick, Wild Bill Hickok
hunts a white buffalo he has seen in a dream.
Hickok moves through a variety of uniquely authentic western locations - dim, filthy, makeshift taverns; freezing, slaughterhouse-like
frontier towns and beautifully desolate high country - before improbably teaming up with a young Crazy Horse to pursue the creature.
Wild Bill Hickok/James Otis, played by Charles Bronson.
Charlie Zane, played by Jack Warden.
Crazy Horse/Worm, played by Will Sampson.
Poker Jenny Schermerhorn, played by Kim Novak.
Whistling Jack Kileen, played by Clint Walker.
Winifred Coxy, played by Stuart Whitman.
The White Buffalo is a 1977 fantasy Western film directed by J.
Lee Thompson and starring Charles Bronson, Kim Novak,
Jack Warden, Slim Pickens and Will Sampson.
The film explores themes of wyoming, usa, saloon, based on
novel or book, buffalo, native american.